这都是什么玩意
What the hell is this mess?
是她干的
She did this.
特意摆成这样
It means something,
一定有什么意思
the way it's all set up like that.
总督派我们来是对的
The governor was right to send us out.
说的对 提姆
Damn straight, tim.
我们这趟来是为民除害
We're doing a righteous public service here.
「回去」
Go back.
啥
What?
手摆成了一个G
The arms are a G.
腿是O
The legs make an O.
最后是一个后背 意思是让我们「回去」
And that's a back. It says "go back".
太有趣了
This is too good.
看啊
Look at this.
她竟然用行尸给咱留言
She sent us a biter-gram, y'all.
这太可怕了
I don't believe this is happening.
你他妈的够了
Hey, hey! You knock it off.
发什么神经呢
What the hell's wrong with you?
总督派你来
Now, the governor chose you.
是相信你能胜任
'cause he thought you were ready.
我也希望你能担当重任
I want you to succeed. I do.
但如果你不停发牢骚
But if you keep announcing to the world.
说自己吓到尿裤子
that you're pissing your pants,
我就打得你满地找牙
I'm gonna have to smash your teeth in.
你姓什么来着
Now how do you say your last name?
加尔朱洛
Gargulio.
我还是继续叫你尼尔吧
Well, I'm gonna keep calling you Neil.
行吧
All right?
你想怎样 米琼恩
What's the deal, Michonne? Hmm?
你要从树林突袭 以一敌四吗
You gonna leap out of the woods, one against four,
我们可都全副武装
All of us armed to the teeth.
你就只有一把杀猪刀
and you with just your little pig-sticker?
机会渺茫啊 米琼恩
No, no, no, Michonne.
玩够了没
We having fun yet?!
《行尸走肉》
你好 有谁在吗
Hello? Is… is someone there?
我在 你是谁
Yes. Yes. Who is…?
我的天
Oh, my god!
真没想到有人会接
I can't believe someone would pick up,
我们从灾难发生后一直在打
we've been calling since it all started.
你在哪
Where are you?
我不能说
I can't say.
你可能在千里之外呢
You could be 1, 000 miles away.
我不能告诉你我们的位置
I'm not going to say where we are.
你们…
Are you…
在安全的地方吗
are you some place safe?
是的
Yeah.
我们靠谨慎才活到现在
And part of it is because we're careful.
我不能告诉你我们在哪儿
I can't tell you where we are.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你们的地方为什么安全
What ma… what makes your place so safe?
因为
It's just…
我们离它们
away…
很远
from them.
我有个儿子
I have a son.
还有个刚出生的孩子
I… I have a newborn baby.
我跟一群人在一起
I'm with a good group of people.
你们愿意…
Would you be willing…
你们愿意让其他人加入吗
Could you take the others?
我们会尽力帮助你们
We can pull our weight. We can help you.
我得跟组织商量一下
I'd have to talk to the group.
让他们听电话 我来说
Well, put them on. Let me make a case.
先让我和他们谈谈吧
Let me talk to them first.
求你了 别挂电话
Please, please, don't… don't go.
求你了 我们是好人
Just… please, we're good people here.
我们需要帮助 我们会帮助你们的
We just need some help and we can help you.
- 两小时后给你回话 - 求你了
- I'll call back in two hours. - Please!
你不明白 你不懂
You don't understand. You don't know.
我们要死了
We're dying.
我们快要死了
We're dying here.
大家都好吗
Everybody okay?
是的 我们很好
Yeah, we are.
你呢
What about you?
我把锅炉房清理干净了
I cleared out the boiler block.
那里有多少行尸
How many were there?
不确定 一打或是两打吧
I don't know. A dozen, two dozen.
我得回去了
I have to get back.
我只是过来看一下卡尔
Just wanted to check on Carl.
瑞克 我们可以去把尸体搬出去
Rick, we can handle taking out the bodies.
- 你不必做 - 不 我一定要做
- You don't have to. - No, I do.
每人都有枪和刀吗
Everyone have a gun and a knife?
是的 不过我们子弹快用光了
Yeah. We're running low on ammo, though.
玛姬和我准备下午出去一趟
Maggie and me were planning on making a run this afternoon.
我们找到个电话本 可以去上面一些地方
Found a phone book with some places we can hit,
找找子弹和婴儿食品
look for bullets and formula.
我们把发电机房清出来了
We cleared out the generator room.
阿克塞尔在那修着呢
Axel's there trying to fix it.
以防万一
in case of emergency.
我们也会把下层清理一下
We're gonna sweep the lower levels as well.
很好
Good. Good.
瑞克
Rick.
我们走 她中枪了
Let's go. She's hit.
走不快的
Slowed her down.
提姆和克罗利 他们…
Tim and Crowley, they…
我们马上就到危险区域了
We're close to the red zone.
枪声会把周围的行尸们引向我们
Them shots just pulled every biter in this area our way.
我们走 起来
Let's go. Get up.
尼尔
Neil!
你现在必须担当起来 孩子
Now you're gonna rise to the occasion, son.
事态很严峻
Some serious shit's going down.
我需要你 你明白吗 小兄弟
I need you here. You read me, amigo?
- 我不想你死 - 我明白
- I don't want you to die. - Yes. Yes.
起来
Get up.
你知道 我们从不让自己人变成行尸
Now, you know, we don't never let our own turn.
永远不
Never.
快点
Come on.
动手
Just do it.
好孩子
Atta boy.
快点 我们走
Come on, let's get going.
她不是在逃跑 她是在猎杀我们
She ain't running. She's hunting.
我们也是 走吧
So are we. There we go.
你可以加入进去
You know you can join in.
他们又不咬人
They don't bite.
安全祥和是这个小镇的主旨
That's kind of the whole idea of the place.
你似乎也鼓励别人
Seems like you also encourage people.
自相残杀啊
to punch each other in the face.
那个角斗场
The arena.
你不喜欢那个 对吧
You didn't like that much, huh?
不太喜欢 但我能理解
No, not so much, but I get it.
听着 我问你点事
Listen, I want to ask you something.
不行
No.
好吧
Okay.
等会 你为什么说能理解
Hold on. How do you get it?
我不会告诉你该怎么管理好你的城镇
I'm not gonna tell you how to run your town.
这是我们的城镇 你留下来了
This is our town. You stayed.
现在也是这里的一分子 告诉我吧
You're part of this now, so tell me.
你们用角斗来发泄逃避 这不好
If it's an escape, I don't think it's the right one.
这是残暴之乐
It's brutality for fun,
我觉得这世界已经够惨烈了
and I think the world's brutal enough already.
角斗令你很烦恼
It really bothered you, huh?
但我确实想待在这儿
But I do want to be here.
那么在你
So what were you saying.
谴责我们的野蛮行为之前 你想说什么
before I made you condemn our sadistic way of life?
我想做贡献 每个人都在尽一份力
I want to contribute. Everyone else does.
你可以在食物区帮罗比
Well, Robbie could use some help in food distr…
我想去墙上放哨
I want to work the wall.
我枪法好 我想在这方面尽点力
I'm a good shot. I want to contribute. I want to stay that way.
你能用弓箭吗
Can you use a bow?
我可以学
I can learn.
我可以找人教你
Well, I can get somebody to teach you.
喂
Hello?
你好
你就是刚才和她通话的人吗
You're the guy she was talking to?
是的
Yes.
你们想来我们这里吗
And you want to come where we are?
- 她说那儿很安全 - 确实安全
- She said it was safe. - It is.
没有行尸攻击 没人被咬
No attacks, no one's been bit,
没有死伤
no one's died,
没人变行尸 没人发疯
no one's turned, no one's gone crazy.
是的 我们想去你们那里
Yes, we want to come where you are.
你们可能是危险人物
You could be dangerous.
你杀过人吗
Have you killed anyone?
杀过 都是威胁我和我团队的人
Yes, people who threatened me or threatened my group.
你杀过多少人
How many people have you killed?
四个
Four.
有两个外人想干掉我
Two outsiders who tried to draw on me.
其中一个把我推向行尸
One threw me to walkers.
另一个曾是我们的成员
The other one, he was one of our own.
但他迷失了
He lost it.
迷失了什么
Lost what?
迷失了自我
Who he was.
他威胁我
He threatened me.
还想杀我 所以我杀了他
He tried to kill me, so I killed him.
你是如何失去你的妻子的
How did you lose your wife?
你怎么知道我有妻子
How do you know I had a wife?
你有个儿子和婴儿
You have a boy and a baby.
告诉我你怎么失去你妻子的
Tell me how you lost your wife.
我不想谈这个
I don't want to talk about that.
喂
Hello?
喂 不
Hello? No!
不
No!
谢谢你教我
Thanks for doing this.
总督下令 义不容辞
When the governor asks me to do something, I do it.
我们可以从明天开始
I figure we can start tomorrow.
有一块训练场地和一些干草垛
There's a training area, some hay bales.
还有把弓可以让你使
There's even a bow you can use.
是我原来的弓
It was my old one.
你肯定很厉害
You must be pretty good.
是的 我爸爸教我的
Yeah. My dad taught me.
他带我打过猎
He used to take me hunting.
他想让我参加奥运会
He wanted me to be in the Olympics.
这把是他的
This one was his.
比我的车还值钱
I mean, it's worth more than my car.
太酷了
It's… awesome.
所以为了这弓我杀了他
So I totally killed him for it.
你杀他才不是这原因呢
That wasn't why you killed him.
不是
No.
爸爸已经不是他自己了 哥哥也不是了
My dad wasn't himself. My brother wasn't either.
我不得不杀了亲妹妹
I had to kill my sister.
很难受 对吧
Sucks, right?
是的
Yeah.
行尸来了
Walker.
看我的
Cool. Watch this.
- 我来吧 - 我可以的
- I got it. - I can do it.
我们不能越过围墙
We're not supposed to go over the wall.
你搞什么啊
What the hell was that?
这么做才对
That is how it's done.
我说了我能行
I said I could do it.
你有毛病吗
What is wrong with you?
这不是游戏
This isn't a game.
我能坐下吗
May I?
还能感觉得到
Still feel it.
我现在在动脚趾呢
I'm wiggling my toes right now.
感觉我膝盖以下还有脚
I'm a ghost from the knee down.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
你救了我的命 瑞克
You saved my life, Rick.
她对之前的事感到很抱歉
She was sorry for the things that happened.
她亲口告诉我的
She told me that.
她打算告诉你的
She planned on telling you.
慢慢来 不要急
Take your time, whatever you need.
你支撑着我们
You carried us.
你没让我们放弃 你带我们到这
You didn't let us give up. You got us here.
还不够 这里不够安全
It's not enough. It's not safe enough.
没什么安全的地方了
There isn't anywhere else.
我知道你想远离这一切
I know you want to get away from this,
但这一切无法逃避
but we've run already.
我接到了一通电话
I got a call.
什么
What?
有人打电话了
Someone called.
打到这个电话上
On this phone.
一个女人
A woman.
她很年轻 她们有一群人
She was young. She was part of a group.
她说他们找到了一个安全的地方
She said they had a safe place.
他们在随机拨打号码 刚好让我接到了
They said they were just dialing numbers and I picked up.
她说他们会再打过来
she said they'd be calling back.
如果可信的话 我想说服他们收留我们
If it sounds right, I want to talk them into taking us in.
她说他们住在哪里了吗
Did she say where they were?
没有 不过没关系
No, but it doesn't matter.
如果安全 我们就过去
If it's safe, we'll get there.
先别告诉其他人
Don't tell the rest of the group. Not yet.
我坐在这陪你
I'll sit here with you.
反正我现在也只能坐着
That's something I'm pretty good at nowadays.
不必
No.
好吧
All right.
你看那里
Check it out there.
肯定是昨晚错过了
Must've missed them last night.
可能有一两个行尸
It's probably just one or two of 'em.
看起来蔫蔫的
Don't look. They got much fight.
就让它们先待在这吧
They ain't going nowhere.
我们回来的时候再处理
We'll take care of it on the way back.
走吧
Come on.
我妈妈嗜酒如命
You know, my mom, she liked her wine.
她喜欢躺在床上吸烟
She liked to smoke in bed.
维珍妮女士香烟
Virginia Slims.
有次我和一群孩子在小区玩
I was playing out with the kids in the neighborhood.
莫尔不在时我就跟他们玩
I could do that with Merle gone.
他们有自行车 我没有
They had bikes. I didn't.
我们听到警笛声越来越响
We heard sirens getting louder.
他们跳上自行车 追过去
They jumped on their bikes, ran after it,
看看有没有什么新鲜事
You know, hoping to see something worth seeing.
我追着他们 但是怎么也追不上
I ran after them, but I couldn't keep up.
我跑过一个拐角时
I ran around a corner.
看到我的朋友们看着我
and saw my friends looking at me.
不 所有人都在看着我
Hell, I saw everybody looking at me.
到处都是消防车
Fire trucks everywhere.
左邻右舍都跑了过来
People from the neighborhood.
起火的地方是我家
It was my house they were there for.
母亲的烟头点燃了床
That was my mom and bed.
化为乌有
Burnt down to nothing.
这可不好受
That was the hard part.
她就这样消失了
You know, she was just gone.
就此蒸发
Erased.
什么都没剩下
Nothing left of her.
人们说这样还好受点
People said it was better that way.
可能吧 只是听上去不那么真实
I don't know. Just made seems like wasn't real.
我射杀了我母亲
I shot my mom.
她休克了
She was out.
还没有变行尸
Hadn't turned yet.
我结束了这一切
I ended it.
这是真实的
It was real.
你母亲的遭遇我很难过
Sorry about your mom.
彼此彼此
I'm sorry about yours.
走吧
Come on.
请进
Come in.
我知道你找我来是为什么
I know why you want to see me.
我们告诉过你
You were told.
不到万不得已不得走出墙外
we don't go over unless we have to.
我只是
I just…
想活动一下
I wanted a little practice.
好吧
Fair enough.
你不用再去墙上了
We don't need you on the wall.
好吧
Okay.
我喜欢那场角斗
I liked the fights.
这感觉令我不好受
I didn't like that I liked them.
但你就是喜欢 我懂
But you did. I know.
什么
What?
你怎么知道
How?
你本可以离开的 曾经打算离开了
Could have walked out. You started walking out.
但你选择了留下
But you stayed.
就像你也没离我而去一样
Just like you stay here right now to tell me that.
你是说我也喜欢你吗
Are you saying that I like you, too?
我觉得你有点喜欢我
I think I'm growing on you.
干得不错啊 小子
You worth the occasion, kid?
回去后和你痛快喝两杯
When we get back, I'm gonna get you a beer.
我们抓紧吧 她坚持不了多久的
Come on, she can't have made it that far.
不不 我们完成任务了
No, no, no, no. We're done.
我们去找辆车子 赶紧回家
We're gonna grab a car, haul ass home.
今天忙活一天了
It's been a good day's work.
但她杀死了提姆和克罗利
But she… she killed Tim and Crowley.
是的 但她的伤也不轻
Yep, but we messed her up pretty bad.
她已经进入了危险区
Anyway, she's headed straight for the red zone.
她死定了
She's as good as dead.
我们跟总督怎么说
What do we tell the governor?
还能怎么说
How you think we tell him?
就说我们杀了她
Tell him we killed her.
我说过 她已经死定了
Like I said, man, she's as good as dead.
不行 我要去追她
I'm gonna keep going.
她脑子不正常
She ain't right in the head.
她必死无疑
She's gonna die.
不值得我们浪费时间
Ain't worth our time.
更不值得我们冒生命危险
Definitely ain't worth our blood.
我们走吧
Now let's go.
事态严峻 这是你亲口说的
This is some serious shit. That's what you said.
在这事上 我不会跟总督撒谎的
I'm not gonna lie to the governor about it.
你是对的
You're right.
不能就这么草草了事
Can't cut corners on this one.
你学得很快 小子
You've come along pretty quick there, kid.
你叫什么名字来着
How do you say your name again?
加尔朱洛
Gargulio.
听见鸟叫了吗
Hear that bird?
加尔朱洛
Gargulio.
喂
Hello?
你不想告诉他你妻子是怎么死的吗
You didn't want to tell him how your wife died?
不 我刚失去她 但如果必须说我会说
No, I just lost her. But if that's what it takes…
说出来是好事
It'd be good.
你该谈谈这事 瑞克
You should talk about it, Rick.
那听上去
That sounds…
怎么
How…
你是怎么知道我名字的
How do you know my name?
外面安全
Clear outside.
好的 我们进去看看
All right, let's take a look.
等等
Hey.
今天是美妙的一天
It's a beautiful day.
格伦 拿上那只鸭子
Glenn, get that duck.
- 啥 - 拿上那只鸭子
- What? - Get that duck.
- 你没开玩笑吧 - 没有
- Are you serious? - Yeah.
一个在监狱里长大的小孩需要点玩具
A kid growing up in a prison could use some toys.
你是那种每周末都给自己车打蜡的人吧
You were the kind of guy who waxed his car every weekend, right?
不是 我的车并不令我特别自豪
No, I wasn't particularly proud of my car.
我的房子 我的工作也如此
or my house, or my job.
我养的狗笨的称得上奇葩
My dog was a wonder of stupidity.
有一次连棵树都没打过
Lost a fight with a tree once.
但你建造了这里
You did this.
我觉得让人难以置信的是
I find it hard to believe that you didn't have a single thing.
你从没有一样引以为豪的东西
that you were proud of before.
我可没那么说
I didn't say that.
我也曾拥有过
I had something.
你多久没那啥了
So how long has it been?
我是说
Uh, since…
你多久没喝到这么好的威士忌了
Since you had whiskey this good?
久到我已记不得了
So long I can't remember.
我很高兴自己忘记了很多
Well, I'm happy to forget a lot.
不仅忘记了那些不好的事
Not just the bad stuff.
也包括那些美好时光吗
Even the good times?
是啊 此时此刻
Yeah. I want to be here.
我只想在这里
Right now.
手里拿着酒杯 清风拂过枝叶
This glass in my hand, leaves in the breeze,
与你畅谈
Talking to you.
我感到很荣幸
I feel special.
能作总督的听众
An audience with the governor.
算了吧
Ugh.
还是叫我菲利普吧 我现在下班了
Let's just go with Philip, huh? I'm off the clock.
菲利普 那样更好
Oh, Philip. That's better.
让我觉得不那么像个说客
Makes me feel less like a lobbyist.
你大可不必为喜欢那角斗而感到羞耻
You don't have to be ashamed about liking the fight.
也不必为参与其中羞耻
Or fighting the fight.
我喜爱它
I love it.
生活不局限于此 可在当下
It's not the only thing, but nowadays,
它又是活着的一部分
It's part of being alive.
真正的活着
Really alive.
大多数人都没有
Most people don't have it,
那种能看到全部事实的能力
what it takes to see the whole story.
能够与它共存 取其为用
Being able to live with it, to use it.
这就是为什么它们众 我们寡
That's why there's a hell of a lot more of them than us.
我们吗
Us?
没错
Yeah.
你有这能力 安德莉亚
'Cause you have it, Andrea.
你做到了
You made it.
那就享受它吧
So enjoy it.
今朝有酒今朝醉 明日死去又何妨
Eat, drink, and be merry, for tomorrow we die.
我可没想过死
Oh, I'm not planning on dying.
是啊 我也不想 可世事无常
No, neither am I. It just happens.
万事皆有可能
Other things happen.
我们刚中了发现奶粉的头奖
We just hit: the powder formula jackpot.
感谢上帝
Oh, thank god.
我还找到了豆子罐头 电池
I also got beans, batteries,
鸡尾酒小香肠 还有很多芥末酱
Cocktail wieners, many mustards.
从这回监狱是一条直路
It's a straight shot back to the prison from here.
说不定能赶上晚餐
Hardly making time for dinner.
我喜欢这里的安静
I like the quiet.
无论在监狱 还是在家
Back there, back home, you can always hear them.
总能听到它们在围栏外面发出的声音
outside the fence no matter where you are.
你们说的这个家在哪儿啊
And where is it y'all good people are calling home?
莫尔
Merle?
你给我退后
Hey, back the hell up!
好啊 好啊 宝贝儿
Okay, okay, honey.
放松点
Jesus.
你还活着
You made it.
能不能告诉我 我弟弟活着吗
Can you tell me, is my brother alive?
是的
Yeah.
你带他来见我 亚特兰大的事儿
Hey, you take me to him and I'll call it even.
我们一笔勾销
on everything that happened up there in Atlanta.
既往不咎 好吗
No hard feelings. Huh?
你喜欢这个吗
You like that?
是啊
Yeah.
我找到了一家医疗用品仓库
Well, I found myself a medical supply warehouse.
自己安了这么个东西
Fixed it up myself.
挺酷的吧
Pretty cool, huh?
我们会告诉达里尔你在这儿
We'll tell Daryl you're here and.
他会过来见你
he'll come out to meet you.
等等啊 等等
Hold on. Just hold up.
淡定 淡定
Hold up here. Hold up.
我们能找到对方就是个奇迹了
Hey, the fact that we found each other is a miracle.
别激动
Come on, now.
你们可以信任我
You can trust me.
你得信任我们
You trust us.
你待在原地
You stay here.
不
No!
别紧张 老兄 别紧张啊
Hey, hey, hold up, buddy, hold up.
放开她 放开她
Let go of her. Let go of her!
立马把枪放车上
Gun in the car, right now.
给我把枪放车上 小伙子
Put it in the car, son.
这就对了 现在来开车兜风吧
There you go. Now we're gonna go for a little drive.
我不会带你回我们营地的
We're not going back to our camp.
不 我们去其它地方
No, we're going somewhere else.
给我上车 格伦 你开车
Get in the car, Glenn! You're driving!
- 快去 - 不要
- Move! - Don't.
好吧
Okay.
起来
Get up.
这就对了
That's it.
这就是我要找的
Oh, that's what I'm talking about.
你好啊 老兄
Yeah, buddy.
你要拖鞋干嘛
What the hell you need slippers for?
世界末日也需要放松嘛 你懂得
You know, end of the day, relaxing.
好吧
All right.
肯定是最尽头牢房里的
Must have been in the cell at the end.
其它地方都查过了
We checked everywhere else.
这是卡萝尔的刀
That's Carol's knief.
你怎么知道我名字
How did you know my name?
因为我们认识你
Because we know you.
你们怎么认识我的
How do you know me?
你也认识他们 瑞克
And you know them, Rick.
今天跟你说话的那些人
The people you were talking to today,
是艾米 吉姆 杰奎
That was Amy, Jim, Jacqui.
洛莉
Lori?
洛莉 洛莉
Lori? Lori?
怎么了 瑞克
What happened, Rick?
宝贝 怎么了
Baby, what happened?
我那么的爱你
I loved you.
我撑不住了
I couldn't put it back together.
我本以为我可以的
I thought I was…
我对自己承诺过
I made a deal with myself.
要让你活下去
I would keep you alive.
我要找到住处 安顿好一切
I'd find a place. I would fix that.
然后…
And then…
我不敢开门 我不能冒险
I couldn't open that door, I couldn't risk it.
我本要让你活下去
I was gonna keep you alive.
让卡尔 孩子都活下去
Carl, the baby. And then…
我以为还有时间
I thought there'd be time.
但时间永远不够
There's never time.
我爱过你
But I loved you.
现在依然爱
I love you.
我坚持不下去了
I couldn't put it back together.
我该早点对你说
I should have said it.
我该早点说爱你的
I should… I should have said it.
瑞克
Rick.
听我说
Now you listen to me.
你还有孩子
You have a baby.
我们的孩子
Our baby.
你有卡尔
And Carl.
和其他人
And the others.
我爱你
I love you.
瑞克
Rick.
拜托你坚持下去
Can you do that?
瑞克
Rick?
Rick? Rick?
我刚说我下班了是假的
I lied when I said I was off the clock.
这工作24小时不间断
This is a 24/7 kind of gig.
要我躲床底下吗
Should I hide under the bed?
不必了
Not this time you won't.
有别人在吗
Company?
怎么了
Yeah.
我们的三个人都死了
We lost all three guys.
提姆 克罗利 还有另一个
Tim, Crowley, the other one.
加尔朱洛
Gargulio.
上帝啊
Jesus.
她砍翻了提姆 用剑刺死了他
Yeah, she cut Tim down, put her sword through him.
行尸冲了过来
Then biters got in the middle of it.
然后我杀了她
Then I got her.
该死
Damn.
我们穿上正装 给他们办个英雄般的葬礼
Well, we'll dress it up. Give 'em a hero's funeral.
你编个故事 就说在找补给时出了岔子
You tell a story. A supply run gone sideways.
你拿到了吗
Do you have 'em?
她的人头和那把刀
Her head. The sword.
当时兵荒马乱的
Um, we got caught in a crowd.
提姆拿着人头 克罗利拿着刀
Tim had the head, Crowley had the sword.
他们全被撕得粉碎
They both got all tore up.
但我找到了点别的
I got something else for you, though.
一个亚特兰大营地的老相识
A guy I used to know from the atlanta camp.
还有他貌美如花的小女友
and his pretty little girlfriend.
- 他们认识安德莉亚吗 - 认识
- They know Andrea? - Mm-hmm.
还有别人吗
Anyone else?
不知道
Don't know.
我是返回路上碰到他们的
Found them on the return trip.
看他们的样子 他们似乎过得不错
From the looks of them, they got to be set up pretty good.
我会找出他们营地的
I'll find out where.
没什么事吧
Everything okay?
当然没事
Hell, yeah.
她长得像你
She looks like you.
抱稳了吗
Hey, just… you got her?
- 是的 - 好的
- Yeah. - All right.
很好
Good.